Guide to the Mark Hall Amitin/ World of Culture for the Performing Arts, Inc. Archive MSS.121
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series I: Personal Papers
  - Subseries E: Playbills, Programs, Flyers, Brochures.
    - An Unfinished Song (Michael Rafkin), 1992 (Box 15, Folder 105)
    - University of Iowa Summer Dance Workshop, undated (Box 15, Folder 106)
    - Up Against It (Kenneth Elliott), 1989 (Box 15, Folder 107)
    - Jean-Claude van Itallie, undated (Box 15, Folder 108)
    - Victory Over the Sun (Robert Benedetti), 1980 (Box 15, Folder 109)
    - Vienna: Lusthaus (Martha Clarke), 1986 (Box 15, Folder 110)
    - The Warrior Ant, 1986 (Box 15, Folder 111)
    - Water Mirror (U Theatre), 1994 (Box 15, Folder 112)
    - Welded (Jose Quintero), 1981 (Box 15, Folder 113)
    - West Bank Cafe, undated (Box 15, Folder 114)
    - We Wont Pay! We Wont Pay! (R.G. Davis), 1980 (Box 15, Folder 115)
    - Whodunnit (Michael Kahn), 1983 (Box 15, Folder 116)
    - Who's Afraid of Virginia Woolf (David Wheeler), undated (Box 15, Folder 117)
    - The Who's Tommy (Des McAnuff), 1993 (Box 15, Folder 118)
    - Wilson in the Promised Land (Adrian Hall), 1970 (Box 15, Folder 119)
    - The Winter's Tale (James Lapine), 1989 (Box 15, Folder 120)
    - The Wiz (Geoffrey Holder), 1977 (Box 15, Folder 121)
    - WNYC Program Guide, Jun 1981 (Box 15, Folder 122)
    - Women Heroes (Gina Wendkos, Helen Ratner), 1986 (Box 15, Folder 123)
    - The Wooster Group, undated (Box 15, Folder 124)
    - The Workroom (Milwaukee Repertory Theatre), 1980 (Box 15, Folder 125)
    - Write if You Get Work (Jeffrey M. Jones), undated (Box 15, Folder 126)
    - Y Chamber Symphony Mar, 1986 (Box 15, Folder 127)
    - Yivo Institute for Jewish Research, 1982 (Box 15, Folder 128)
    - You Can't Take it With You (Ellis Rabb), 1966 (Box 15, Folder 129)
    - You're a Good Man Charlie Brown (Joseph Hardy), Jan 1968 (Box 15, Folder 130)
    - The Yueh Lung Shadow Theatre, undated (Box 15, Folder 131)
    - Paul Zaloom, undated (Box 15, Folder 132)
    - Zoot Suit (Luis Valdez), 1979 (Box 15, Folder 133)
  - Subseries F: Professional Writing (Mark Hall Amitin)
    - JoAnne Akalaitis, Denitra Vance, undated (Box 16, Folder 1)
      Offsite Barcode: 31142040617311
    - Alone at the Beach, 1993 (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - "Amongst Friends is the Enemy Within", 1993 (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - Asian American Film Festival, 1993 (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - Bailiwick Repertory, 1993 (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - Bay Street Theatre Festival, 1992 (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - Julian Beck interview transcript, undated (Box 16, Folder 7)
    - Benefit Advocates, May 21, 1993 (Box 16, Folder 8)
    - Eric Bogosian, 1991 (Box 16, Folder 9)
    - Fernando Botero, 1966-1993 (Box 16, Folder 10)
    - Books requested for interview, 1992 (Box 16, Folder 11)
    - Breakdown Services, 1994 (Box 16, Folder 12)
    - Joseph Brodsky interview, July 6, 1993 (Box 16, Folder 13)
    - Steve Buscemi, 1997 (Box 16, Folder 14)
    - Chelsea Clinton News& The Westsider, August 6, 1993. (Box 16, Folder 15)
    - Chinese Art (for Black Book), February 1998. (Box 16, Folder 16)
    - "A Crown of Scorns" (for The Hamptons), 1992 (Box 16, Folder 17)
    - Robert Crumb, H.R. Giger, undated (Box 16, Folder 18)
    - Willem Dafoe, 1992 (Box 16, Folder 19)
    - Decoding Utopia proposal, 1991 (Box 16, Folder 20)
    - Anne Duquesnay, 1996 (Box 16, Folder 21)
    - Experimental Theatre, undated (Box 16, Folder 22)
    - Experimental Theatre - proposal for TV series, 1979 (Box 16, Folder 23)
    - Karen Finley, 1991 (Box 16, Folder 24)
    - Fall Fashion, 1991 (Box 16, Folder 25)
    - Fall 1993 theatre season (for The Advocate) (Box 16, Folder 26)
    - Fire Island News, 1994 (Box 16, Folder 27)
    - The Firm information folder, 1993 (Box 16, Folder 28)
    - John Frohnmayer, Jul 31, 1992 (Box 16, Folder 29)
    - "From Beck to Albee and Back Again: My Life Around Art", 1994 (Box 16, Folder 30)
    - The Fugitive, 1993 (Box 16, Folder 31)
    - Diamanda Galas material, 1992 (Box 16, Folder 32)
    - The Galleries of East Hampton, 1993 (Box 16, Folder 33)
    - Philip Glass, 1992 (Box 16, Folder 34)
    - Spalding Gray, 1992 (Box 16, Folder 35)
    - The Hamptons, 1992 (Box 16, Folder 36)
    - Hamptons Magazine, 1993 (Box 16, Folder 37)
    - Hamptons Magazine- various, undated (Box 16, Folder 38)
    - Hamptons Magazine/ Evan Schindler, undated (Box 16, Folder 39)
    - Julie Harris, 1993 (Box 17, Folder 1)
      Offsite Barcode: 31142040617329
    - Hocus Pocus, Road Scholar, 1992 (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - Hot Shots, 1993 (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - House of Angels, undated (Box 17, Folder 4)
    - Timothy Hutton interview, 1993 (Box 17, Folder 5)
    - The Illusion, 1994 (Box 17, Folder 6)
    - "The Intifada Blues: Israeli and Palestinian Theatre at a Crossroads", [1994] (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - Eugene and Franne Lee, Mark Amitin, ABook on Design, undated (Box 17, Folder 8)
    - Roy Lichtenstein, 1994 (Box 17, Folder 9)
    - Manhattan Murder Mystery, undated (Box 17, Folder 10)
    - Married to it, Barton Fink, undated (Box 17, Folder 11)
    - "Media Meanness and Madness", undated (Box 17, Folder 12)
    - "New Theatre in a New China", 1979 (Box 17, Folder 13)
    - NYQ letter, November 12, 1991. (Box 17, Folder 14)
    - Our Town, 1993 (Box 17, Folder 15)
    - "Positive Thinking", undated (Box 17, Folder 16)
    - Reno interview, 1993 (Box 17, Folder 17)
    - "Repression: A Simple White Paper", 1973 (Box 17, Folder 18)
    - Robin Hood: Men in Tights, 1992 (Box 17, Folder 19)
    - "Rock in Russia", 1981 (Box 17, Folder 20)
    - Romper Stomper, The Long Day Closes, Orlando, undated (Box 17, Folder 21)
    - Saturday Review, August 1977. (Box 17, Folder 22)
    - Searching for Bobby Fisher, The Secret Garden, 1993 (Box 17, Folder 23)
    - Serious Fun at Lincoln Center, 1992 (Box 17, Folder 24)
    - Small claims court: Amitin vs. Enlightenment Press, 1993 (Box 17, Folder 25)
    - Spy, 1991 (Box 17, Folder 26)
    - Edgar Tafel, undated (Box 17, Folder 27)
    - "Theatre in China: Beyond the Great Wall", 1980 (Box 17, Folder 28)
    - "The Theatre of China: An Inside View", undated (Box 17, Folder 29)
    - Theatre Rhinoceros, 1993 (Box 17, Folder 30)
    - Three Tall Women, 1994 (Box 17, Folder 31)
    - True Romance, Kalifornia, undated (Box 17, Folder 32)
    - "Touring for the Masses", undated (Box 17, Folder 33)
    - Paula Vogel interview, July 1, 1993. (Box 17, Folder 34)
    - Wendy Wasserstein interview, July 1, 1993. (Box 17, Folder 35)
  - Subseries G: Dissertation, datebooks, journals.
    - Dissertation notes, undated (Box 18, Folder 1)
      Offsite Barcode: 31142040617337
    - Dissertation notes, June 1976. (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - Dissertation notes, including photocopies of photographs of The Living Theatre and San Francisco Mime Troupe., undated (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - Dissertation notes, undated (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - Dissertation notes, undated (Box 18, Folder 5)
    - Dissertation notes, undated (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - Dissertation notes, illustrations, including photographs of The Living Theatre, The Performance Group, San Francisco Mime Troupe, Bread and Puppet Theatre, Le Plan K, Theatre Now, El Teatro Campesino, and drawings by Julian Beck, undated (Box 18, Folder 7)
    - Dissertation - text in French (copy), undated (Box 18, Folder 8)
    - Dissertation - French original 1, 1976 (Box 18, Folder 9)
    - Dissertation - French original 2, undated (Box 18, Folder 10)
    - Dissertation - French original 3, undated (Box 18, Folder 11)
    - Datebook, 1970 (Box 18, Folder 12)
    - Datebook, 1971 (Box 18, Folder 13)
    - Datebook, 1972 (Box 18, Folder 14)
    - Datebook, 1973 (Box 18, Folder 15)
    - Datebook, 1974 (Box 18, Folder 16)
    - Datebook, 1975 (Box 18, Folder 17)
    - Datebooks, 1976 (Box 19, Folder 1)
      Offsite Barcode: 31142040617345
    - Datebooks, 1978 (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - Datebooks, 1980 (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - Datebooks, 1981 (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - Datebooks, 1983 (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - Datebooks, 1988 (Box 19, Folder 6)
    - Datebooks, 1989 (Box 19, Folder 7)
    - Datebooks, 1990 (Box 19, Folder 8)
    - Datebooks, 1991 (Box 19, Folder 9)
    - Datebooks, 1992 (Box 19, Folder 10)
    - Datebooks, 1995 (Box 19, Folder 11)
    - Datebooks, 1997 (Box 19, Folder 12)
    - Datebooks, 1998 (Box 19, Folder 13)
    - Autographs, 1961 (Box 20, Folder 1)
      Offsite Barcode: 31142040617360
    - Diplomas, 1961 (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - James Alfred Spicer memorial service guest book, January 31, 1979. (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - Journals, 1971 (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - Journals, 1971 (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - Journals, 1972 (Box 20, Folder 6)
    - Journals, 1973 (Box 20, Folder 7)
    - Journals, 1974 (Box 20, Folder 8)
    - Journals, 1974 (Box 20, Folder 9)
    - Journals, 1976 (Box 20, Folder 10)
    - Journals, 1976-1978 (Box 20, Folder 11)
    - Journals, 1979 (Box 20, Folder 12)
    - Journals, 1980 (Box 20, Folder 13)
    - Journals, 1981-1982 (Box 21, Folder 1)
      Offsite Barcode: 31142040617352
    - Journals, 1982 (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - Journals, 1983 (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - Journals, September., 1983 (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - Journals, October., 1983 (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - Journals, 1982-1984 (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - Journals, 1983-1984 (Box 21, Folder 7)
    - Journals, 1984 (Box 21, Folder 8)
    - Journals, 1984 (Box 21, Folder 9)
    - Journals, 1985 (Box 21, Folder 10)
    - Journals, 1985 (Box 21, Folder 11)
    - Journals, 1985 (Box 21, Folder 12)
    - Journals, 1985-1987 (Box 21, Folder 13)
    - Journals, 1986 (Box 21, Folder 14)
    - Journals, 1986 (Box 21, Folder 15)
    - Journals, 1987 (Box 22, Folder 1)
      Offsite Barcode: 31142040617378
    - Journals, 1988 (Box 22, Folder 2)
    - Journals, 1988-1989 (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - Journals, 1990 (Box 22, Folder 4)
    - Journals, 1991 (Box 22, Folder 5)
    - Journals, 1993 (Box 22, Folder 6)
    - Journals, 1993 (Box 22, Folder 7)
    - Journals, 1993 (Box 22, Folder 8)
    - Journals, 1994 (Box 22, Folder 9)
    - Journals, 1995 (Box 22, Folder 10)
    - Journals, 1996-1998 (Box 22, Folder 11)
    - Notebooks, undated (Box 22, Folder 12)
    - Notebooks, undated (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - Subseries H: Personal correspondence
    Scope and Contents note
    Some letters are undated or unclearly dated. Dates given here may not be accurate or inclusive because in folders with more than one letter only legible dates are given.
    - Tommy Ace, 1981-1987 (Box 23, Folder 1)
      Offsite Barcode: 31142040617386
    - Carole Allegro, 1974-1984 (Box 23, Folder 2)
    - Dave Allen, 1983 (Box 23, Folder 3)
    - Niels Alsing, 1975-1977 (Box 23, Folder 4)
    - Mark Amitin to parents, 1974-1976 (Box 23, Folder 5)
    - Amitin family, 1976-1998 (Box 23, Folder 6)
    - Amitin family, 1976-1998 (Box 23, Folder 7)
    - Amitin family, 1976-2001 (Box 23, Folder 8)
    - Raphael Amor, 1976 (Box 23, Folder 9)
    - Chuck Andreatta, 1972-1979 (Box 23, Folder 10)
    - David Archer, undated (Box 23, Folder 11)
    - Joe Badgett, 1977 (Box 23, Folder 12)
    - Sammy Barros, 1979-1986 (Box 23, Folder 13)
    - Michael Bartuccio, 1974-1980 (Box 23, Folder 14)
    - Bill Bastian, undated (Box 23, Folder 15)
    - Julian Beck, 1985 (Box 23, Folder 16)
    - Henrik Bindslev (contains large charcoal drawing), undated (Box 23, Folder 17)
    - Ron Blanchette, 1973-1984 (Box 23, Folder 18)
    - Mark Bluver (Living Poem Theatre Workshop), 1976 (Box 23, Folder 19)
    - Valerie Bousquet, 1976 (Box 23, Folder 20)
    - Michel Breton, 1972-1980 (Box 23, Folder 21)
    - Nadje Brouwers, 1976 (Box 23, Folder 22)
    - Richard P. Brown, 1972-1976 (Box 23, Folder 23)
    - Brad Burns, 1977 (Box 23, Folder 24)
    - Michael Buscemi, 1998 (Box 23, Folder 25)
    - Steve Buscemi & Jo Andres, 1990-1998 (Box 23, Folder 26)
    - David Callaghan, 1986-1996 (Box 23, Folder 27)
    - Thom Cardwell, 1974-1982 (Box 23, Folder 28)
    - Erico Carneiro, 1975-1979 (Box 23, Folder 29)
    - Cenicola family, 1975 (Box 23, Folder 30)
    - Jian Chen (see also Series I, Subseries B), 1984 (Box 23, Folder 31)
    - David Cooper-Wall, 1979 (Box 23, Folder 32)
    - Paula Court, 1987-1994 (Box 23, Folder 33)
    - Joe Daerec, 1972-1979 (Box 23, Folder 34)
    - Fritz de Boer, 1984-1989 (Box 23, Folder 35)
    - Nick de Martino, 1996 (Box 23, Folder 36)
    - Paco de Zela, 1975-1994 (Box 23, Folder 37)
    - Jean Michel di Berardino, 1977 (Box 23, Folder 38)
    - Elizabeth Does, 1969-2001 (Box 23, Folder 39)
    - Dorfman family, 1986-1997 (Box 23, Folder 40)
    - Jango Edwards (Friends Road Show, Festival of Fools), 1975-1978 (Box 23, Folder 41)
    - Bob and D.J. Ehrhardt (parents of Theo), 1985-1994 (Box 23, Folder 42)
    - Theo Ehrhardt, 1970 (Box 24, Folder 1)
      Offsite Barcode: 31142040617394
    - Theo Ehrhardt, 1973 (Box 24, Folder 2)
    - Vickie Ellis, 1974 (Box 24, Folder 3)
    - Emerson College, 1966 (Box 24, Folder 4)
    - Lars Erikson, 1981 (Box 24, Folder 5)
    - Peter Facinelli, 1993-1996 (Box 24, Folder 6)
    - Marie-Helene Falcon, 1983 (Box 24, Folder 7)
    - Jean Pol Ferbus, 1975-1979 (Box 24, Folder 8)
    - Kevin Ferguson, 1975 (Box 24, Folder 9)
    - Joey Fernando, 1985-1992 (Box 24, Folder 10)
    - John Finch, undated (Box 24, Folder 11)
    - Roy Forsythe, 1974-1988 (Box 24, Folder 12)
    - Fernando Fougares, 1976-1979 (Box 24, Folder 13)
    - Leon Fried, 1978-1992 (Box 24, Folder 14)
    - Philip-Dimitri Galas, 1977 (Box 24, Folder 15)
    - Tomas Gaspar, 1980 (Box 24, Folder 16)
    - Tim Glavin, 1975 (Box 24, Folder 17)
    - Wolfgang Glitscher, 1973-1979 (Box 24, Folder 18)
    - David Goble, 1974 (Box 24, Folder 19)
    - Andrew M. Gold, 1980 (Box 24, Folder 20)
    - Robin Gold, 1974 (Box 24, Folder 21)
    - William H. Graff, 1971 (Box 24, Folder 22)
      File Plan
    - Urs Grimlinger, 1982-1987 (Box 24, Folder 23)
    - Cesar Guarnero, 1982 (Box 24, Folder 24)
    - Joe Hackett, 1993-1997 (Box 24, Folder 25)
    - Rusty Halverson, 1979 (Box 24, Folder 26)
    - Brian Hardy, 1976-1981 (Box 24, Folder 27)
    - Michael Haykin, 1977 (Box 24, Folder 28)
    - Bob Hueck, 1974 (Box 24, Folder 29)
    - Philip Hitchens, 1979-1994 (Box 24, Folder 30)
    - Hannes Jaenicke, 1984-1989 (Box 24, Folder 31)
    - Jeff Janisheski, 1989-1998 (Box 24, Folder 32)
    - Jim Jarmusch, Sara Driver, April 26, 1984. (Box 24, Folder 33)
    - Guo Ji-De, 1980-1984 (Box 24, Folder 34)
    - Cecil O. Johnson, 1980-1985 (Box 24, Folder 35)
    - Mark Jones, 1978 (Box 24, Folder 36)
    - Richard Katz, 1977-1980 (Box 24, Folder 37)
    - Avy Kaufman, 1987 (Box 24, Folder 38)
    - Martin Kaufman, 1971-1973 (Box 24, Folder 39)
    - Cyrus Khambatta, 1987-1997 (Box 24, Folder 40)
    - Jeroen Klaasse, 1976 (Box 24, Folder 41)
    - Doug James Knott, 1978-1995 (Box 24, Folder 42)
    - Michelle Kokosowski, 1976-1987 (Box 24, Folder 43)
    - Lili Kolarovics, 1973 (Box 24, Folder 44)
    - Daniel Lannuzel, 1973-1976 (Box 24, Folder 45)
    - Sally Lapiduss, 1988-1998 (Box 24, Folder 46)
    - Gil Lazier, 1973 (Box 24, Folder 47)
    - Franne Lee, 1988 (Box 24, Folder 48)
    - Mark Jordan Legan, 1982-1988 (Box 24, Folder 49)
    - Michael Le Mense, 1972-1975 (Box 24, Folder 50)
    - John V. Lindsay, 1984 (Box 24, Folder 51)
    - Jeff Loeser, 1975 (Box 24, Folder 52)
    - Albert Larken, 1973-1979 (Box 24, Folder 53)
    - Karen Ludwig, undated (Box 24, Folder 54)
    - Roland Mabille, 1976 (Box 24, Folder 55)
    - Bill McGlone, 1973-1975 (Box 24, Folder 56)
    - Susan McRae, 1972 (Box 24, Folder 57)
    - John A. Mancini, 1979 (Box 24, Folder 58)
    - Fredric Mao, 1988 (Box 24, Folder 59)
    - Brad Martin, 1991-1994 (Box 24, Folder 60)
    - Wayne Maugans, 1993-1998 (Box 24, Folder 61)
    - Jim Mellon, 1978 (Box 24, Folder 62)
    - Jeffery Messersmith, 1973 (Box 24, Folder 63)
    - Charles R. Mills, 1980 (Box 24, Folder 64)
    - Cliff Mooney, 1980 (Box 25, Folder 1)
      Offsite Barcode: 31142040617402
    - Rebecca Moore, 1988 (Box 25, Folder 2)
    - Bob Morgan, 1972-1977 (Box 25, Folder 3)
    - Julien Motu, 1972-1979 (Box 25, Folder 4)
    - Richard Niles, 1970-1980 (Box 25, Folder 5)
    - Zohar Nir, 1996 (Box 25, Folder 6)
    - Karsten Nyvang, 1984 (Box 25, Folder 7)
    - Glyn O'Malley, 1977-1979 (Box 25, Folder 8)
    - Kevin Sean O'Malley, 1979 (Box 25, Folder 9)
    - Vicki Ooi, 1979 (Box 25, Folder 10)
    - Serge Ouaknine, 1975-1986 (Box 25, Folder 11)
    - Serge Ouaknine, 1976-1997 (Box 25, Folder 12)
    - Jeff Palmer, 1974-1992 (Box 25, Folder 13)
    - Rick Parets, 1976 (Box 25, Folder 14)
    - Rob Parker, 1979 (Box 25, Folder 15)
    - Nicolas Perrot, 1975-1980 (Box 25, Folder 16)
    - Maria Piscator, undated (Box 25, Folder 17)
    - Kaaren Prather, 1973-1979 (Box 25, Folder 18)
    - Robert Projansky, 1980-1993 (Box 25, Folder 19)
    - Rosemary Quinn, 1980-1995 (Box 25, Folder 20)
    - Bill Rampelt, 1983-1984 (Box 25, Folder 21)
    - Nina Rasmussen, 1974-1980 (Box 25, Folder 22)
    - Michael Redington, 1982 (Box 25, Folder 23)
    - Ray Reed, 1972-1989 (Box 25, Folder 24)
    - Don Reilly, 1983 (Box 25, Folder 25)
    - Hanon Reznikov, 1990 (Box 25, Folder 26)
    - Danielle Riche, 1972-1974 (Box 25, Folder 27)
    - Jacques Richier, 1983-1987 (Box 25, Folder 28)
    - Martin Rimann, 1982 (Box 25, Folder 29)
    - River, 1976 (Box 25, Folder 30)
    - Nicole Roegiers, 1972 (Box 25, Folder 31)
    - Luc Rogmans, 1976 (Box 25, Folder 32)
    - Didier Rostoucher, 1976-1980 (Box 25, Folder 33)
    - Arthur Sainer, 1976-1983 (Box 25, Folder 34)
    - Eric Samson, 1979 (Box 25, Folder 35)
    - Joel Sarman, 1982 (Box 25, Folder 36)
    - Hans Schano (The Living Theatre), 1972 (Box 25, Folder 37)
    - Reinhard Schultz, 1973-1981 (Box 25, Folder 38)
    - David Scott, 1980 (Box 25, Folder 39)
    - Michael Scott, 1985-1988 (Box 25, Folder 40)
    - Jeffery Lyle Segal, 1979-1991 (Box 25, Folder 41)
    - Lissa Sexton, 1993 (Box 25, Folder 42)
    - Nitzan Sharron, 1997 (Box 25, Folder 43)
    - Evan Shin, 1983-1997 (Box 25, Folder 44)
    - Mary Shultz, 1994-1999 (Box 25, Folder 45)
    - Michael Shurtleff, 1968 (Box 25, Folder 46)
    - Sven Erik Skovlund, 1982-1987 (Box 25, Folder 47)
    - Snow family (Jess, David, Jay), 1978-1999 (Box 25, Folder 48)
    - Peter Snow, 1979-1985 (Box 25, Folder 49)
    - Joey Sobel, 1981-1999 (Box 25, Folder 50)
    - Patrick Sommier, 1973 (Box 25, Folder 51)
    - David Soria, 1983-1997 (Box 25, Folder 52)
    - James Spicer, 1974-1979 (Box 25, Folder 53)
    - David Suderman, 1976 (Box 25, Folder 54)
    - Robert Sugarman/ Bennington College, 1969-1970 (Box 25, Folder 55)
    - Ken Swiger, 1974 (Box 25, Folder 56)
    - Freddy Sycip, 1979-1981 (Box 25, Folder 57)
    - Serge Taieb, 1976-1989 (Box 25, Folder 58)
    - Harriet Taylor, 1969-1987 (Box 25, Folder 59)
    - Bill Thompson, 1979 (Box 25, Folder 60)
    - Boris Tissot, 1970-1976 (Box 25, Folder 61)
    - Chris Torch (Jordcirkus), 1974-1999 (Box 25, Folder 62)
    - Srecko Trutanic, 1981-1995 (Box 25, Folder 63)
    - Jean-Claude van Itallie, 1980-1999 (Box 25, Folder 64)
    - Stephanette Vendeville, 1977-1991 (Box 25, Folder 65)
    - Paul von Canon, 1989 (Box 25, Folder 66)
    - Mark Wagner, 1975 (Box 25, Folder 67)
    - Julian Wake, 1971 (Box 25, Folder 68)
    - Tom Walker (The Living Theatre), 1979-1995 (Box 25, Folder 69)
    - Francois Weil, 1976-1980 (Box 25, Folder 70)
    - Jurgen Wietlake, 1976 (Box 25, Folder 71)
    - Ben Yaeger, 1995 (Box 25, Folder 72)
    - Paul Zaloom, 1988 (Box 25, Folder 73)
    - A (last names), 1977-1983 (Box 26, Folder 1)
      Offsite Barcode: 31142040617410
    - B (last names), 1972-1999 (Box 26, Folder 2)
    - C (last names), 1972-1997 (Box 26, Folder 3)
    - D (last names), 1972-1992 (Box 26, Folder 4)
    - E (last names), 1972-1993 (Box 26, Folder 5)
    - F (last names), 1972-1992 (Box 26, Folder 6)
    - G (last names), 1973-1999 (Box 26, Folder 7)
    - H (last names), 1972-1997 (Box 26, Folder 8)
    - I (last names), 1980-1989 (Box 26, Folder 9)
    - J (last names), 1973-1986 (Box 26, Folder 10)
    - K (last names), 1977-1992 (Box 26, Folder 11)
    - L (last names), 1972-1992 (Box 26, Folder 12)
    - M (last names), 1972-1993 (Box 26, Folder 13)
    - N (last names), 1972-1991 (Box 26, Folder 14)
    - O (last names), 1982-1994 (Box 26, Folder 15)
    - P (last names), 1972-1999 (Box 26, Folder 16)
    - Q (last names), 1975-1992 (Box 26, Folder 17)
    - R (last names), 1972-1997 (Box 26, Folder 18)
    - S (last names), 1969-1998 (Box 26, Folder 19)
    - T (last names), 1971-1985 (Box 26, Folder 20)
    - V (last names), 1976-1990 (Box 26, Folder 21)
    - W, X (last names), 1975-1994 (Box 26, Folder 22)
    - Y, Z (last names), 1980-1987 (Box 26, Folder 23)
    - A (first names), 1972-1997 (Box 26, Folder 24)
    - B (first names), 1973-1992 (Box 26, Folder 25)
    - C (first names), 1978-1991 (Box 26, Folder 26)
    - D (first names), 1971-1993 (Box 26, Folder 27)
    - E (first names), 1970-1984 (Box 26, Folder 28)
    - G (first names), 1972-1985 (Box 26, Folder 29)
    - I (first names), 1982 (Box 26, Folder 30)
    - J (first names), 1972-1998 (Box 26, Folder 31)
    - K (first names), 1973 (Box 26, Folder 32)
    - L (first names), 1975-1985 (Box 26, Folder 33)
    - M (first names), 1971-1980 (Box 26, Folder 34)
    - O (first names), 1973-1982 (Box 26, Folder 35)
    - P (first names), 1976-1997 (Box 26, Folder 36)
    - R (first names), 1976-1993 (Box 26, Folder 37)
    - S (first names), 1975-1992 (Box 26, Folder 38)
    - T (first names), 1975-1982 (Box 26, Folder 39)
    - V (first names), undated (Box 26, Folder 40)
    - W (first names), 1978-1982 (Box 26, Folder 41)
    - Unidentified correspondents, 1969- (Box 26, Folder 42)
    - Unidentified correspondents, 1975- (Box 26, Folder 43)
    - Memorials for friends, 1983-1987 (Box 26, Folder 44)
    - Box 27 contains unsorted cards and postcards., undated (Box 27, Folder data_value_missing_0c601103199d1ff847a3556584bab30c)
      Offsite Barcode: 31142040617428
  - Subseries I: Business files, theatre companies, flyers, general correspondence
    - Absolute Reality Theatre, undated (Box 28, Folder 1)
      Offsite Barcode: 31142040617436
    - Academic Tours, undated (Box 28, Folder 2)
    - Acadamie Experimentale des Theatres, 1998-2001 (Box 28, Folder 3)
    - AIDS Walk, 1988 (Box 28, Folder 4)
    - Alternative Features Service, 1971 (Box 28, Folder 5)
    - Alternative Theatre Newsletter, 1975 (Box 28, Folder 6)
    - American Branch of International Artist, 1980 (Box 28, Folder 7)
    - American College Theatre Festival, 1982 (Box 28, Folder 8)
    - American College Theatre Festival, 1983 (Box 28, Folder 9)
    - American College Theatre Festival, 1984 (Box 28, Folder 10)
    - American College Theatre Festival, 1985, 1991 (Box 28, Folder 11)
    - American College Theatre Festival, 1986 (Box 28, Folder 12)
    - American College Theatre Festival, 1989 (Box 28, Folder 13)
    - American Theatre Association convention, 1973 (Box 28, Folder 14)
    - American Theatre Association convention, 1979 (Box 28, Folder 15)
    - American Theatre Association convention, 1981 (Box 28, Folder 16)
    - American Theatre Association convention, 1983 (Box 28, Folder 17)
    - Amherst College visit, February 7-8, 1990. (Box 28, Folder 18)
    - Ernest Amitin, 1973 (Box 28, Folder 19)
    - Ernest and Gladys Amitin travel to CA, 1986 (Box 28, Folder 20)
    - Mark Hall Amitin biographical material, 1986 (Box 28, Folder 21)
    - Amitin book catalogue, 1972 (Box 28, Folder 22)
    - Amitin course and workshop proposals, 1977- (Box 28, Folder 23)
    - Amitin film reviews, undated (Box 28, Folder 24)
    - Amitin - Frommer article, November 5, 1981. (Box 28, Folder 25)